[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
And so let's actually use the model.
让我们真正地用一下这个模型
So, next we've now trained a liner regression model, let's evaluate it.
我们已经创建了一个线性回归模型 现在我们来评估一下它
So, what we're gonna do next is
所以我们接下来要做的是
#Evaluate the simple model.
#评估这个模型
So how to evaluate it?
怎么来评估它呢？
We're gonna look at the test data.
我们得看一看测试数据
So, remember we had the split test data.
还记得我们有分离的测试数据
Let's understand test data a little bit.
让我们稍微看一下这个测试数据
So, for example, let's print.
举个例子 我们求一下...
For the test data, for
测试数据...
the price column, what's the average price?
价格那一列的平均值
What's the mean price?
平均价格是多少呢？
So this just computes the average price and the average price for
我们计算出测试数据的平均价格
the test data, for this data from Seattle is $543,000.
对西雅图来说 这个价格是$543,000
That's how average house costs, it's pretty expensive actually.
这是平均的房屋价格 真的不便宜啊
Now, we've built a square foot model, and so
我们之前已经建立了平方尺模型
what we want to do is evaluate it on this test data.
我们想做的是用这个测试数据评估一下平方尺模型
So we're going to take the sqft_model
我们将会用到我们建立的sqft_model
that we built and we're gonna call what's called evaluate function.
然后调用它的评估函数
Which can take a test data set and print out or
我们将测试数据作为输入变量 它会打印或者
return some statistics of how well that fit is doing.
返回一些数据告诉我们这个模型拟合得有多好
So let's do that.
让我们回车
So, I'm actually going to type, print in the beginning,
我要把 print 敲在最前面
because it formats it a little bit nicer.
因为这样排版更好看些
And you'll see that the maximal error over all test houses was 4.1 million.
你会看到所有测试数据的最大误差是410万
So there was one house that was an outlier, it was really badly predicted.
所以 其中有一个房子的数据是异常值 它导致这个模型预测得很不准确
And average error, so the RMSE, so the root means squared error,
它的平均误差 RMSE 也就是均方根误差
we talked about this.
我们之前谈到过它
Emily talked about this with us during the lectures,
Emily在之前的课程中谈到过这一概念
is $255,000, so that's the RMSE.
均方根误差 (RMSE) 是$255,000
So we built this simple model, we tested, has pretty high RMSE,
所以我们建立了一个模型 我们测试它 并得到了很高的RMSE
but let's look at some predictions it tries to make from the data.
我们接着来看一下它由这些数据做出的一些预测
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community